Objective:
BLU are the Fluttershys with the ability to freeze ponies by meleeing them.

Fluttershy thinks it's harmless fun, but RED knows better. The only way to stop her is to kill her!

BLU wins by freezing everypony or surviving until the time runs out. RED wins by killing all of the Fluttershys.

Other Notes:

BLU plays melee only medic. RED can pick from all classes except Engineer, Spy, and Medic.

Meleeing teammates thaws them out. Help your buddies out with a good whack, you'll want them to return the favor later!